[{"id": 1324, "question": "Growing up in one of the poorest, most crime-ridden communities on the south side of Atlanta, US, being raised by a single mother who didn't finish 3rd grade, living each day on food stamps and attending what the media called \"the most dysfunctional public school district,\" not many people expected much of me, so I had to expect something of myself. On my 13th birthday, I bought a poster of Harvard to hang in my room. Being at Harvard became what I dreamt about: I saw myself attending class in Sanders Theater, studying in Widener Library and eating in Annenberg Hall. Even when my electricity was cut off and I woke up at 5:30 a.m. to pitch blackness, I knew that my poster of Harvard was still hanging only two feet away from me. I'd begin my day by asking myself these two questions, \"What do...\n\nQ: What can we conclude from the text?", "options": ["Applying to a famous university is important.", "It is essential to set yourself an ambitious goal as early as possible.", "Poor people usually have greater goals than others.", "You should be determined to act and make decisions in order to achieve your goals."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1149, "question": "Planning to go to a gym? If you are one of those who have spent many days planning to join a gym or to attend it regularly, then why not choose some home exercise? Here are some home exercises without equipment. Jumping jacks This one is the best home workout without weights which is a great exercise that will work your hands and legs. Perform this exercise by standing with your feet placed together and arms at your sides. Now tuck in your abs and jump by bending in your knees. At the same time, move your feet apart as much as you can and raise your hands to bring in line with your shoulder. While you come back you must be in a starting position, feet together, hands at sides and knees bent. You must land on your heels and again jump. Jogging Jogging is one of the best home exercises witho...\n\nQ: What is the right order of your body parts during rotation exercise?", "options": ["hands--legs---back----legs.", "wrists--hands---feet---shoulders", "wrists---feet---shoulders---legs", "hands---shoulders---knees---legs"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 986, "question": "People can be addicted to different things -- e.g. alcohol, drug, certain foods, or even television. People who have such an addiction are compulsive :They have a very powerful psychological need that they feel they must satisfy. According to psychologists, many people are compulsive spenders. They feel that they must spend money. This compulsion, like most others, is impossible to explain reasonably. For compulsive spenders who buy on credit , charge accounts are even more exciting than money. In other words, compulsive spenders feel that with credit, they can do anything. Their pleasure in spending large amounts is actually greater than the pleasure that they get from the things they buy. There is even a special psychology of bargain hunting. To save money, of course, most people look fo...\n\nQ: What is the text mainly about?", "options": ["The psychology of money-spending habits.", "The habits of compulsive spenders.", "A special psychology of bargain hunting.", "The use of the psychology of spending habits in business."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 741, "question": "\"Now I just don't believe that.\" Surely all of us, at some point, have watched a movie and thought: It's simply badly researched, or, the makers must think we're fools. If movies were completely scientifically accurate, they'd probably be as interesting as a Physics 101 lecture. In real life, there are no explosions in space, gas usually doesn't explode from a lit cigarette, and Bruce Willis / Jackie Chan / Will Smith would most likely be in a coma after getting kicked in the head. Recently, the British newspaper The Daily Telegraph ran a humorous piece on unconvincing tech moments from some top movies. Let's see what _ are all about. Telegraph writer Tom Chivers' first example is from the end-of-the-world movie Independence Day, in which a character comes up with a virus capable of destro...\n\nQ: What does the text mainly deal with?", "options": ["Plots of some famous movies.", "Characters in space movies.", "Popularity of space movies.", "Mistakes made in some movies."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2057, "question": "From the same place that brought you the Robot Suit HAL comes the \"motorized knee\".Designed by researchers at Japan's Tsukuba University, the device supports the flex( ) of the knee, which enables a runner to use 30% less muscle power compared to running unassisted. Coming in a kit , the device consists of a small motor that helps flex the knee, a sensor that detects the knees' degree of flex, and a safety lever --all of which attach to the user's leg.The user is also forced to carry a backpack that holds a control unit and battery to power the motor.All up the device weighs around 5kg,which will probably lessen the performance benefits of wearing the device somewhat.In experiments runners wearing the device could jog at 7.5kmh, which is hardly anything special--but predictably they could ...\n\nQ: In which column of a newspaper would this passage be found?", "options": ["Science.", "Health.", "Education.", "Business."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 452, "question": "No one is sure how the ancient Egyptians built the pyramids near Cairo. But a new study suggests they used a little rock'n'roll. Long-ago builders could have attached wooden poles to the stones and rolled them across the sand, the scientists say. \"Technically, I think what they're proposing is possible,\" physicist Daniel Bonn said. People have long puzzled over how the Egyptians moved such huge rocks. And there's no obvious answer. On average, each of the two million big stones weighed about as much as a large pickup truck. The Egyptians somehow moved the stone blocks to the pyramid site from about one kilometer away. The most popular view is that Egyptian workers slid the blocks along smooth paths. Many scientists suspect wokers first would have put the blocks on sleds . Then they would h...\n\nQ: Why is rolling better than sliding according to West ?", "options": ["Because more force is needed for sliding.", "Because less preparation on path is needed for rolling.", "Because sliding on smooth road is more dangerous.", "Because rolling work can be done by fewer cattle."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2952, "question": "Have you ever been to a wedding and simply loved the bride's bouquet ?More than likely some part of it was the Hawaiian Wedding Plant. This foreign houseplant can be enjoyed by anyone, not just brides. With a little proper attention and careful planning on location, this foreign houseplant, which is from Madagascar, can be brought into the home where it can become an interesting focus. Caring for the Hawaiian Wedding Plant is not much different from caring for any other houseplants that may already be in your home. The only difference between this type of houseplant and others is the amount of the basic requirements that this foreign houseplant needs to survive and perform beautifully. During the growing season, this plant requires its wet soil, but when winter rolls around, this plant nee...\n\nQ: The Hawaiian Wedding Plant comes from  _  .", "options": ["Hawaii", "China", "Madagascar", "Alaska"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 389, "question": "We've all felt discouragement at one point or another in our lives. However, when this emotion bleeds into other aspects of our life, it can sometimes be inappropriate or even harmful. I was personally discouraged by an adult during my high school. After telling her what university I wanted to attend, she plainly told me I would not get in. I was completely shocked and angry at her statement. The adult may have not intended to hurt me with her words, but it had an after effect. The meeting made me think she had no belief that I could possibly succeed in the future. After that it caused me to try to avoid any future meeting with adults until absolutely necessary. We are all human; therefore, we can all understand that some days are more challenging. But when people allow situations of stres...\n\nQ: The passage is mainly about   _  .", "options": ["the adults' roles in school", "the skill to encourage students", "the way to communicate with children", "the importance of personal professional growth"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2816, "question": "The idea of light pollution has developed with the increase of lights in cities. In many areas, this light makes it difficult or impossible to observe stars and planets in the night sky. There are a number of reasons why light pollution is important. One has become clear at the Mount Wilson Observatory near Los Angeles, California. Today, light from Los Angeles makes the night sky above Mount Wilson very bright. It is no longer an important reasearch center because of light pollution. Light pollution threatens to reduce the scientific value of research telescoples in other important observatories. They include Lick Observatory near San Jose, California and Yerkes Observatory near Chicago, Illionis. Light pollution is the result of wasted energy. Bright light that shines into the sky is not...\n\nQ: Which of the following is TRUE according to the passage?", "options": ["Mount Wilson Observatory is the most important one in America.", "Light pollution affects observatories only.", "In the dark night people can observe the sky clearly.", "Astronomers can observe the stars clearly by the lights of the cities."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 845, "question": "If you are looking for the place that has everything, there is only one place to visit, and that's New York. It's a whole world in a city. The World of Theater: All of New York is a stage. And it begins with Broadway. Where else can you find so many hit shows in one place? Only in New York! The World of Music: Spend an evening with Beethoven at Lincoln Center. Swing to the great jazz of Greenwich Village. Or rock yourself silly at the hottest dance spots found anywhere. The World of Art: From Rembrandt to Picasso. From Egyptian tombs to Indian teepees. Whatever kind of art you like, you will find it in New York. The World of Fine Dining: Whether it's roast Beijing duck in Chinatown, lasagna in little Italy, or the finest French coq au vin found everywhere, there is world of great taste wai...\n\nQ: Which of the following can visitors do only in New York?", "options": ["To see the Statue of Liberty.", "To taste the finest French coq au vin.", "To enjoy a Beethoven concert.", "To eat Roast Beijing Duck."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3225, "question": "\"For those who haven't been to Tibet is a dream; for those who have already been there, Tibet is a memory.\" said Li Wan, a graduate from Zhongshan University. \"For me, living there is my dream and happiness.\" Li was suddenly crazy about Tibet after working there for three months as an office clerk. Since 2008, Li has spent most of her time travelling in Tibet. Four years have passed and she has been almost every corner of Tibet. Li came to Tibet firstly because of her desire for personal freedom. She entered Tibet along the Yunnan-Tibetan road, enjoying the special view happily. She was surprised to find that it is a white paradise on earth. Although she couldn't even speak a word of Tibetan language, she had no difficulty in communicating with natives. \"To me, they are free, generous, sim...\n\nQ: According to the last two passages, we can see Li Wan is a   _   person.", "options": ["determined", "simple", "proud", "pretty"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2527, "question": "TANG Dynasty writer Du Mu once wrote in a poem titled Qingming: \"The ceaseless drizzle drips all the dismal day; So broken-hearted fares the traveler on the way.Where can a wine house be found to drown his sadness ?A cowherd points to Almond Flower (Xing Hua) Village in the distance.\" Qingming, the traditional tomb-sweeping day on the Chinese lunar calendar, falls on April 4 this year. Qingming Jie was proclaimed a Chinese national holiday in 2008. It is a time for remembering loved ones who have departed . People visit their ancestors' graves to sweep away the dirt and get rid of any weeds. They also leave offerings of food and flowers, and burn incense and paper money. Chinese tombs are usually built in the woods or on mountains, far from the city. It is believed that an area that faces ...\n\nQ: The writer write the passage in order to  _   .", "options": ["enable us to observe traditional tomb-sweeping day.", "show traditional and present ways to spend Qingming Festival .", "educate people to show their respect to the ancestors", "raise people's awareness of environmental protection."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3303, "question": "Street art can be found on buildings, sidewalks, street signs and even trash cans from Tokyo to Paris to New York City. This special kind of art can take the form of paintings, sculptures, cloth or even stickers. Street art has become part of a global visual culture. Now, even art museums and galleries are collecting the work of street artists. It is not easy to provide an exact history of the street art movement. This kind of art has developed in many kinds of ways in places all over the world. Also, because it is illegal to paint public and private property without permission, street artists usually work secretly. This secretive nature of street art and its countless forms make it hard to define exactly. And people have different opinions about the movement. Some think street art is a cr...\n\nQ: They best title of the passage is  _  .", "options": ["The way to become a street artist.", "What does Graffiti art stand for?", "The history of an art movement.", "The work of street artists."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1272, "question": "Spring is the time to go out and enjoy the weather and scenery.Here are some events to attend in March of 2012 in Oregon! Oregon Country Fair(OCF), 9 am to 7 pm on March 8 - 10 OCF first started in 1969, and it's blossomed into an outstanding example of what a non - profit should be. OCF is an event of shopping & atmosphere, and food ranging from Indian & Afghani cuisine to Italian & France cuisine.Wonderful craft & music never stop.From the time you get there until the time you leave, everyone has a smile on their faces, and they wave and say hello.For tickets, go and visit www.Oregoncountryfair.org. 30thAnnual Seaside Beach Volleyball Tournament, 8 am to 6 pm on March 12 - 14 The Annual Seaside Beach Volleyball Tournament is an amateur tournament that draws amateur volleyball players to ...\n\nQ: If Lisa wants to learn more about an outing in Oregon, she may visit   _  .", "options": ["www.Seasideor.com.", "www.Hoodtocoast.com.", "www.aadfv.blogspot.com.", "www.Oregoncountryfair.org."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3114, "question": "Then comes July, and with it examinations, but these are soon finished and with them ends the school year. Boys and girls have nearly two months' holiday before them as they leave school by train and car to return home to their fathers and mothers. The summer holidays are the best part of the year for most children. The weather is usually good, so that one can spend most of one's time playing in the garden or, if one lives in the country, out in the woods and fields. Even if one lives in a big town, one can usually go to a park to play. The best place for a summer holiday, however, is the seaside. Some children are lucky enough to live near the sea, but for the others who do not, a week or two at one of the big seaside towns is something that they will talk about for the whole of the follo...\n\nQ: Children like the seaside so much, because they can   _  .", "options": ["swim in the sea", "play with the sand", "take a sun bath", "do all of the above"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2696, "question": "BERLIN---A German woman, fearful that a burglar was trying to break into her second -storey apartment, called police after she heard someone climbing up to her balcony shortly after midnight, police said Thursday. Police discovered the \"burglar\" was a man carrying flowers and a bottle of wine who turned out to be the woman's boyfriend. But then arrested him on an outstanding reason. \"He was trying to surprise her with the flowers and a bottle of wine but it all went wrong,\" said Korbach police spokesman Volker Koenig. He said the man jumped down from the balcony and tried to escape but was quickly caught by police. \"He gave the police who were taking him to jail the bottle of wine as a gesture of thanks for the friendly treatment after the arrest. \" Koenig said. LONDON---A smoker who died ...\n\nQ: The man climbing up to the girl's balcony   _", "options": ["was actually a wanted thief", "was put into prison in the end", "thanked the police for setting him free", "was treated badly by the police"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 102, "question": "People in Mutsuhito, Japan, lived through one hundreds, and sometimes thousands, a day.But they couldn't get used to it. What was it? It was a string of earthquakes that made the small town shake all the time.This went on for more than a year.Sometimes the quakes were very small.Only certain instruments could pick them up.At other times, the quakes damaged houses and land.The people were always afraid.They wished they knew how to stop the ground from shaking. People all over the world would like to know when an earthquake is coming.But an earthquake is almost always a surprise.Under the surface of the Earth, huge blocks of rock drift apart or slide against each other.The ground above splits apart or rumbles and shakes. Some scientists hope to predict quakes by keeping a close watch on anim...\n\nQ: How does a fault form?", "options": ["When California rests on two separate plates.", "When the plates end up on top of each other.", "Before an earthquake happens.", "After volcano comes."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1317, "question": "Recently educators have been questioning \"prep school\" (=preparatory school) where barely literate high school athletes get their transcripts by taking courses occasionally and sometimes by taking no courses at all. The athletes then go on to famous sports universities, where they exhaust their playing years before landing back on the streets without job opportunity or college degrees. The prep school scheme was meant to avoid academic qualification rules for college athletes made years ago by the National Collegiate Athletic Association. The N.C.A.A., which was slow to recognize the seriousness of the problem, has finally adopted policies to root it out. But those policies will not do the job unless everyone is involved, including prep schools and college athletics departments that still ...\n\nQ: About students in \"prep school\", which of the following facts might NOTbe true?", "options": ["Most of them are good at different kinds of sports events.", "They can easily be admitted to a university by cheating.", "After they graduate from university, they will usually find promising jobs.", "They seldom have good academic performance at high school."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3370, "question": "My dad is a wonderful man.He worked hard all his life and has never let me down.if one person influenced me to go to college and become a better person, it's him. Every morning my dad would wake up at 4 am.He would do some writing and then Ieave for work.He would get off work at 5 pm and spend the remaining day with his family.Any time I needed him,he was there.He was a great role model.My dad is a typical family man.He supports us financially and emotionally.He bends over backward to support his family. My dad is the reason why I try to support my son as much as I can.He is also the reason why I have decided to spend less time with friends and more time with family.Now I'm a much better woman.I once worked hard at my studies in school and now do well in my work.My dad became a manager in ...\n\nQ: We can infer from this passage that  _  .", "options": ["the author is proud of his father very much", "the author's husband has become a manager", "the author's father was too busy to be with her", "the author has moved back and lived with her father"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1439, "question": "I'm usually fairly skeptical about any research that concludes that people are either happier or unhappier or more or less certain of themselves than they were 50 years ago. While any of these statements might be true, they are practically impossible to prove scientifically. Still, I was struck by a report which concluded that today's children are significantly more anxious than children in the 1950s. In fact, the analysis showed, normal children aged 9 to 17 exhibit a higher level of anxiety today than children who were treated for mental illness 50 years ago. Why are America's kids so stressed? The report cites two main causes: increasing physical isolation brought on by high divorce rates and less involvement in community, among other things and a growing perception that the world is a ...\n\nQ: The author thinks that the conclusions of any research about people's state of mind are   _  .", "options": ["illogical", "confusing", "surprising", "questionable"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 315, "question": "In today's Internet age, online games can be a change from the pressure of school and work. However, they can also cause problems and unhealthy addictions. This is most clearly seen in the example of South Korea. This country has the world's highest percentage of high-speed Internet services. It also has a high number of game players who are addicted to online games. In 2004, a young man died after playing online games almost nonstop for 86 hours. A 12-year-old boy stole $16,000 from his father to continue online games which he could not get away from. Such problems are spreading to other parts of Asia as well. In 2005, it was reported that about 80 percent of China's 13.8 million online game players were under 25. And many of these were said to be addicted. Such numbers point toward a gro...\n\nQ: In the passage, the writer tells us a fact that   _  .", "options": ["South Korea has a large number of Internet schools", "more and more young men are stealing money for online games", "China's online game players are all under the age of 25", "online game addiction is a very common problem in South Korea"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 547, "question": "Introductory Chemistry was taught at Duke University for many years by Professor Bonk.One year, two guys took the class and did pretty well on all the quizzes and midterms.They each had a solid A.These two friends were so confident in going into the final that the weekend before the final week, despite the Chemistry final being on Monday, they decided to go to the prefix = st1 /UniversityofVirginiato party with some friends. They had a great time there.However, with their hangovers and tiredness, they overslept all day Sunday and didn't make it back to Duke until early Monday morning.Rather than taking the final then, they found Professor Bonk after the final and explained to him how they missed the final.They told him they went up to the University of Virginia for the weekend and had plan...\n\nQ: It can be inferred from the passage that   _  .", "options": ["Bonk wasn't strict with the two guys", "Bonk didn't believe the two guys' explanation", "the two guys came back to campus late on purpose", "repairing the flat tire took the two guys a lot of time"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2432, "question": "Big Brothers Big Sisters is based on the simplicity and power of friendship. It is a program which provides friendship and fun by matching _ (ages 7-17) with a volunteer adult who can be both a role model and a supportive friend. Volunteer tutors come from all walks of life--married, single, with or without children. Big Brothers and Big Sisters are not replacement parents or social workers. They are tutors: someone to trust, to have fun with, to talk and go to when needed. A Big Sister and Little Sister will generally spend between one and four hours together three or four times each month for at least twelve months. They enjoy simple activities such as a picnic at a park, cooking, playing sport or going to a football match. These activities improve the friendship and help the young perso...\n\nQ: Why  did  Sarah  want  to  get  involved  in  the  program?", "options": ["She used to be a volunteer.", "She felt a bit bored with her life.", "She needed a part-time job.", "She wanted to get a challenging job."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1303, "question": "Signing up for a digital TV service provides you with access to over 200 channels from all over the globe. However, television today is dominated by adult language, making it hard for concerned families to find channels suitable for young eyes. Therefore, most movie channels are automatically removed form the list of TV channels for an entire family. The following are some good ones based on popularity on a global scale. Discovery Channel Discovery and its many channels can be considered as the founding father of informative channels on television. What National Geographic does in a scholastic manner, Discovery tries to do in an entertaining manner--educating the masses about anything and everything. Fox Family Finding a movie channel that broadcasts pictures suitable for teenagers and kid...\n\nQ: Which of the following can best describe Discovery Channel?", "options": ["Relaxing.", "Touching.", "Commercial.", "Professional."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 406, "question": "The literal meaning of philosophy is \"love of wisdom\". But this meaning does not tell us very much. Unlike the other disciplines ,philosophy cannot be defined by what you study, because it is actually unlimited. Anything can be the subject matter of philosophy: art, history, law, language, literature, mathematics, medicine, psychology, religion, science, and values. Philosophy is one of the world's oldest subjects of study, and in fact, the other academic disciplines are directly related to philosophy. For this reason you get a Doctorate of Philosophy (Ph.D.) in biochemistry, or computer science, or psychology. Two broad sub-fields of philosophy are logic and the history of philosophy. Logic is the science of argument and critical thinking. It provides sound methods for distinguishing good...\n\nQ: From the passage, we can conclude  _  .", "options": ["not all the subjects have to do with philosophy", "a person will get a Ph.", "philosophy can be helpful for the study of any other subjects", "philosophy is the only solution to all the problems to the world"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 539, "question": "It was 11 pm. Donald Lubeck was lying in bed. Outside, lightning lit up the sky, and thunder shook the house. Suddenly he heard the smoke alarm sounding. Lubeck walked down to see what happened; he opened the door to the kitchen, and flames just went out. The sudden strong wind from the doorway immediately created a large fire from a small one, probably caused by lightning. Lubeck went back to his bedroom to call 911. \"I felt safe because the room had a separate stairway,\" he explains. The phone didn't work, and when Lubeck tried to go down the stairway, he was stopped by a wall of flames. Lubeck realized he was in trouble. His daughter and granddaughters, who lived with him, were away for the night. Up a hill lived Lubeck's neighbors, Jeremie Wentworth and his wife. From his house, Wentwo...\n\nQ: Which of the following words can best describe Jeremie Wentworth?", "options": ["Patient and creative.", "Calm and brave.", "Careful and clever.", "Simple and generous."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2121, "question": "The worst days of any summer are the rainy ones. We spend all year looking forward to nice weather and long, hot days. In winter, with its cloudy days and bitter cold, we dream of those days at the beach, lying on the sand and enjoying the bright and burning sun. And then, summer comes, and it rains. As a child, I would wake up to rainy summer days and come close to crying. It wasn't fair. We suffered through months of school and experienced bad weather for those short ten weeks of freedom. On those rainy summer days, I had nothing fun to do and could only sit inside, staring out at the rain like a bird in a cage. I was an only child, so there was no one else to play with. My father worked from home, so I was not truly alone, but he could not actively play with me since he was at work. It ...\n\nQ: When the author was a child, he   _  .", "options": ["liked staying indoors", "hated rainy days", "dreamed on summer days", "preferred cooler weather"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 412, "question": "Soon after you have your first child, the question of having a second one is raised by friends and family. However, as the pattern of having two children in a family is challenged by modern family units, there are a few reasons why it is not selfish to want only one child. Today, the role of women has changed a lot. But nowadays, a wife has to help her husband earn the bread and butter as well as well as looking after her family. In demanding times like these, a woman has to put in more physical and emotional effort than any other member of the family. Raising a child comes at a cost that remains only heard of, until you find yourself paying it. The good reality of double income with no kids suddenly comes crashing down when there is a child involved in the picture. When one parent (the mo...\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOT mentioned in the passage to support the writer's opinion?", "options": ["better education.", "meaningful childhood.", "less generation gap.", "better care."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2574, "question": "Have you ever heard the saying \" _ \"? Here is how a new teacher made friends with the girls and boys in her class on the first day of school. As the bell rang, the teacher smiled at each girl and boy. Then she said in a quiet voice, \"Good morning. How nice it is to have all of you in my class this year. I'd like to know each of you. I am sure we will enjoy working together.\" Everyone felt that she meant what she said because of her sweet voice and her friendly look. She told the girls and boys her name and wrote it on the blackboard. Then she told them some of the things she liked to do and she was hoping to do with them during the year. Then she said to the class, \"Now you know my name and the things I like and I want to know your names and the things you like. Then I will feel that I kno...\n\nQ: The teacher's sweet voice and her friendly look   _  .", "options": ["made every girl and boy happy", "told the girls and boys everything about herself", "showed that she would like to be a friend of the girls and boys'", "meant she wanted to tell the boys and girls something interesting"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1524, "question": "The atmosphere and oceans are not the only parts of the environment being damaged. Rain forests are being quickly destroyed as well, and their survival is questionable. E.O. Wilson, a biologist at Harvard, called the depletion of rain forest areas \"the greatest extinction since the end of the age of dinosaurs\". Unlike some environmental issues, rain forest depletion has fortunately received significant public and media attention. Despite the opposition to the cutting down of rain forests, the problem continues. Every year, Brazil chops down an area of forest the size of the state of Nebraska. In addition to the Amazon's rain forests, many other forests are being cut down as well. In Indonesia, Zaire, Papua-new Geinea, Malaysia, Burma, the Philippines, Peru, Colombia, Bolivia, and Venezuela...\n\nQ: In the opinion of the author,   _   are being destroyed terribly at present.", "options": ["the rain forests", "the oceans", "the atmosphere", "all the above"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2048, "question": "It was just three degrees above zero. \"That's cold,\" thought Jane as she got ready to deliver her morning papers. Jane has 50 customers, and on cold mornings when she couldn't ride her bike, it took her more than an hour to make her rounds. As she collected her papers and put them into a big canvas bag, Jane regretted that she hadn't finished her math homework the night before. There was still time. She'd hurry with the papers and finish the math before breakfast. Less than an hour later, Jane was nearly finished. She had only five customers to go. She could then head for home to complete her math while her mom fixed breakfast. As she rounded the corner, she saw a car in the middle of the street. It was Mr. Zimmerman, the elderly man who walked with a walking stick. His car was out of gas....\n\nQ: Jane delivers her papers   _  .", "options": ["before she goes to school", "on cold mornings", "with the help of Mr. Zimmerman's car", "on the way to school"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1607, "question": "My father never wanted his children to know what he did for a living.Dad worked in Plant C.Lying beside lake Erie, it saw him in at sunrise and out at nightfall.Sometimes my mother would take my siblings and me to the public beach in our hometown of Ashtabula.she'd gather us round.and point to the smokestacks, coughing clouds into the sky. \"Wave to daddy!\" she'd shout. Four little hands would shoot into the air. I never knew what Dad did in Plant C, but during 34 years of hard work, he had surgery on his shoulder and hand. At 48, he had his first heart attack. He retired in 1993, right after the last kid graduated from college.But the damage was done.A few years later, the next heart attack killed him. I saw my dad in Plant C only once, when l took dinner to him. That night, I looked at my...\n\nQ: Which of the following is TRUE of the facts about the author's father?", "options": ["He didn't suffer a heart attack until he retired", "He worked in Plant C for 48 years in all.", "He was satisfied with his job.", "He always faced danger while working."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 654, "question": "Lee Ann Laraway has polio and is not able to move very much. Most things are out of reach for her. Jeannie, a Labrador retriever, acts as her arms and legs. Jeannie understands 72 or more different commands. On a shopping trip, she can get money for Lee Ann at the bank or candies at the store. She can pay the cashier and get change back. Jeannie brings things to Lee Ann and puts them in her lap. Jeannie was trained at a place called Canine Companions for Independence, located on twelve acres of land in Santa Rosa (California). The land was donated by the cartoonist Charles Shultz. \"We train four different types of dogs here,\" said Ken Kirsh, a dog trainer there. \"Hearing dogs, service dogs, skilled companion dogs, and facility dogs.\" Trainers work with Labrador retrievers and golden retrie...\n\nQ: What kind of dogs are not trained in the center?", "options": ["Dogs that warn their owners of sounds like doorbells.", "Dogs that help their blind owners cross over a road.", "Dogs that open the door for their owners.", "Dogs that work with children who have polio."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2546, "question": "The historic center of Vienna has been added to UNESCO's World Cultural Heritage list. Thus, St. Stephen's Cathedral, the Imperial Palace and many other historic buildings are now recognized as being among the 700 outstanding cultural and natural monuments of mankind - others include the Pyramid Fields from Giza to Dahshur, the historic center of Rome, the Kremlin with the Red Square, the Chinese Wall, the Taj Mahal and the Grand Canyon. Vienna's historic center, in its unity, is considered one of the most beautiful city landmarks in Europe. Three eras left their mark on the former residence of the Habsburgs: the Middle Ages with Gothic St. Stephen's Cathedral whose spire points toward heaven, one of Vienna's landmarks; the Baroque whose most important achievement is the Imperial Palace wi...\n\nQ: What is the passage mainly about ?", "options": ["The universal value of the world heritage in Vienna", "Vienna's becoming one of the cultural and natural monuments of mankind", "The introduction of the historic center of Vienna", "The special culture atmosphere of the historic center of Vienna"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1992, "question": "On the morning of November 18, 1755, an earthquake shock Boston. John Winthrop, a professor at Harvard College, felt the quake and awoke. \"I rose\", Winthrop wrote, \"and lighted a candle, looked at my watch, and found it to be 15minutes after four.\" John Winthrop hurried downstairs to the grandfather clock. It had stopped three minutes before, at 4:12. Except for stopping the clock, the quake had only thrown a key from the mantel to the floor. The clock had stopped because Winthrop had put some long glass tubes he was using for an experiment into the case for safekeeping. The quake had knocked the tubes over and blocked the pendulum .Winthrop, therefore, had the key on the floor. The quake had thrown _ forward in the direction of the quake' s motion by a shock coming from the northwest, per...\n\nQ: The selection suggests that  _  .", "options": ["earthquakes are common in Boston", "John Winthrop was a scientist", "John Winthrop often had difficulty in sleeping", "Harvard College was a center for earthquake researching"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2378, "question": "Tim Welford, aged 33, and Dom Mee, aged 30, both from England, were keen on (=\"like...\" very much) rowing boats. They made a plan to row across the Pacific Ocean from Japan to San Francisco. The name of their rowboat was \"Crackers\". It was about seven meters long. They set out from Japan on May 17,2001. They had rowed nearly 5,500 miles when their boat was hit by a fishing ship on September 17,2001. Luckily they both escaped unharmed, but their boat was badly damaged and they had to abandon( =\" stop)their\" journey. In a radio interview, Dom expressed his disappointment and explained how the accident took place. \"A fishing ship came towards us with nobody on the bridge and ran us down. It all happened so quickly. I managed to dive into the water. Tim felt it would be safer to stay on board....\n\nQ: 43. Dom said that the most important thing in this accident was that   _   .", "options": ["their rowboat was not damaged", "both of them existed after a dangerous time", "they enjoyed this journey", "they failed to reach San Francisco"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 824, "question": "There are millions of used cell phones in the world today. Most of them just lay in our houses without any purpose. Every day dozens of new cell phone models appear. Today, you can find what was regarded as a fantasy yesterday in store and you will buy it tomorrow. But what to do with the old phones, which work well enough and not so old? Just get some money! Simply Sellular is buying almost all models of cell phones: LG, Motorola, Siemens, Samsung, Sanyo, Nokia and many other cell phones. Also they accept phones produced in every country, and in every condition. Simply Sellular can offer a good price for your old cell phone in cash. Their mission is giving you a simple way to get money for an old phone, as simple and profitable, as possible. Also they offer a trade-in scheme to get anothe...\n\nQ: Selling a used cell phone to Simply Sellular, you will get   _  .", "options": ["a good price for the phone in cash", "another new model without any pay", "a cost-free service provided by it", "a profitable plan after the sale"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1434, "question": "Life is full of sweet surprises for Chinese pop singer Edell. She majored in design in a Canadian college. But when she was looking for a job after graduation, she found herself rising as a star in singing. Then she became a hostess on TV. \"These are roles I never expected to take,\" she said. Edell is open to every possibility in life, not afraid to try new things. She says that every day she tries to get herself ready to take any chance that occurs in life. \"My mom told me chance only rewards those with a prepared mind,\" she said. \"So I've tried to explore my potential talents. Thus I won't be at a loss when the right opportunity comes up.\" Edell learned ballet in her childhood until she broke her back in practice. She then fell in love with music. Like many girls of her age, she has a ri...\n\nQ: What is the best title of the passage?", "options": ["Learn from Edell", "Prepare for your chances", "Try to be a singer", "Do learn English well"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2756, "question": "\"I would almost rather see you dead,\" Robert S. Cassatt, a leading banker of Philadelphia, shouted when his twenty-year-old eldest daughter announced that she wanted to become an artist. In the 19th century, playing at drawing or painting on dishes was all right for a young lady, but serious work in art was not. And when the young lady's family ranked among the best of Philadelphia's social families, such an idea could not even be considered. That was how Mary Cassatt, born in 1844, began her struggle as an artist. She did not tremble before her father's anger. Instead, she opposed him with courage and at last made him change his mind. Mary Cassatt gave up her social position and all thought of a husband and a family, which in those times was unthinkable for a young lady. In the end, after...\n\nQ: How did Mr Cassatt react when his daughter made her announcement?", "options": ["He feared for her life.", "He warned her.", "He nearly killed her.", "He was very angry."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2016, "question": "The old lady was glad to be back at the block of flats where she lived. Her shopping had tired her and the basket had grown heavier with every step of the way home. In the lift her thoughts were on lunch and a good rest, but when she got out at her own floor, both were forgotten in her sudden discovery that her front door was open. She was thinking that she must tell her daily maid the next morning to lock the door, and then she remembered that she had gone shopping after the maid had left and she knew that she had turned both keys in their locks. She walked slowly into the hall and at once noticed that all the room doors were open, yet following her regular practice she had shut them before going out. Looking into the living room she saw a sight of confusion over by her writing desk. It w...\n\nQ: She realized burglars had been in the flat when   _  .", "options": ["she found the front door open", "she saw the living room was out of order", "she found the burglars quarrelling among themselves", "she saw a body by her desk"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3329, "question": "Trees should only be pruned when there is a good and clear reason for doing so and , fortunately, the number of such reasons is small. First, pruning may be done to make sure that trees have a desired shape or size.The object may be to get a tree of the right height, and at the same time to help the growth of small side branches which will thicken its appearance or give it a special shape.Secondly, pruning may be done to make the tree healthier.You may cut diseased or dead wood, or branches that are rubbing against each other and thus cause wounds.The health of a tree may be encouraged by removing branches that are blocking up the centre and so preventing the free movement of air. One result of pruning is that an open wound is left on the tree and this provides an easy entry for disease, b...\n\nQ: Pruning should be done to   _  .", "options": ["make the tree grow taller", "improve the shape of the tree", "get rid of the small branches", "make the tree grow taller"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1862, "question": "Polynesian Cultural Center The Polynesian Cultural Center (P.C.C.) offers the best value for your vacation dollar. There is so much to see and do for the entire family. They offer a unique and authentic view not only of the Hawaiian culture, but also offer a taste of their Polynesian cuisines . The Gateway Buffet Package A fun activity for all ages, experience the beauty of true Polynesia with The Polynesian Cultural Center's newest package. Experience the 7 Polynesian Islands as they share with you their culture through song and dance. Enjoy Prime Rib & Seafood Dinner at the Gateway Restaurant, finishing the evening with the Horizons Night Show. Adult Price: $68.00 Child Price: $51.00 The Twilight Package--Ambassador's Fine Dining This activity is an excellent choice for those who want a ...\n\nQ: What can we learn from the above four packages?", "options": ["The Twilight Package--Ambassador's Fine Dining is the cheapest one.", "The 7 Polynesian Islands are included in all the packages.", "The Horizons Night Show may be of special interest to tourists.", "You can enjoy Ali'i Luau Feast if you choose The Gateway Buffet Package."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2776, "question": "How To Apply for USA Passports Online If you live in the United States, and you're planning a trip abroad, it is important to apply for new passports at least 2 months in advance (to avoid extra charges for an expedited passport processing). You can now get the application for a passport online. Some directions are detailed below: Downloading the passport application: The USA passport application, Form DS-11, is available for download on the US Department of State's website. *The passport application form is a Portable Document Format (PDF) file, and your computer must have Adobe Acrobat Reader to open it. If you do not have Adobe Acrobat Reader, you must first download the Adobe Acrobat software. You can do so by clicking here. *If you would like to download a blank application, click her...\n\nQ: When traveling abroad, you may fail to check in if you   _  .", "options": ["wear a different coat from the one in your passport photo", "cut your hair short", "dye your hair into a different color1", "wear sunglasses"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 588, "question": "It's a fact that we all dream. Some dreams seem to last for hours, others only for seconds. Some of us have strange dreams, some have interesting dreams, and some of us have unpleasant dreams. Tests in the 1980s showed that these dreams occur within 90-minute cycles, each cycle made up of six stages. In the last stage people experience rapid eye movement, known as REM, and it is in this stage that dreaming takes place. Eighty percent of people who were woken during this sixth stage could easily remember their dreams. On the other hand, when during the first five stages (NREM), only seven percent could describe a dream. However, of these same people woken during the first five stages, 74% were able to remember thinking activity, although they would not call it a dream. NerysDee, who has wri...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements about dreams is TRUE?", "options": ["Everyone dreams but very few can recall what they dream.", "Some people have long dreams and others have very short ones.", "People can only remember unpleasant dreams.", "More than eighty percent of people can remember their dreams."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2172, "question": "Summer school is something a kid will never forget.For some, it's a way to advance past their classmates.For most, summer school is' a requirement in order to graduate with their classmates I can remember being forced into taking a summer school course.It was not the school that forced me into this awkward situation it was my mother. I was a 16-year-old kid in a new school; My school did not offer summer courses so I had to take my course at an alternative school in the city.It was an experience I will never forget.I was not concerned with making friends.I was there to get credit for a course that I should have received credit for the previous semester.It was.my doing that landed me in the situation and it was important that I understood this. The fees were lowest but the experience was am...\n\nQ: Most students go to the summer school in order to   _  .", "options": ["find good jobs graduation", "become top students in their class", "have a chance to make more friends", "graduate successfully on time"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3304, "question": "Jack was born without eyes. He's very lucky with his timing. He grew up having other kittens to play and socialize with, and was used to people from the moment he was born since there are always kids hanging around the barn. He was a favorite amongst the students at the barn. However, when it came time to find the kittens homes, no one knew where Jack would end up. That's when I got an e-mail from my friend. All she asked was \"Do you still want one of the kittens? There's one here with no eyes and no one can take him.\" Without thinking I told her that I did want the kitten. When we first brought him home Jack walked cautiously around, sniffing everything. He went through a time when he could climb the stairs, but couldn't get down. He would sit at the top and cry until someone came and got...\n\nQ: When Jack first came to the author's house, he   _  .", "options": ["would cry when he felt lonely", "was very happy and played wildly in the room", "had difficulty getting down the stairs", "always needed someone to guide him"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 29, "question": "My favourite book is The Adventure of Tom Sawyer by Mark Twain.Tom lives with his aunt Polly in a quiet street of St. Petersburg, Missouri.He's a lively and clever young boy,and he finds himself in many exciting adventures.He runs away with his two friends,Huck Finn and Joe,to an island in the middle of the Mississippi River for several days.With Huck he goes looking for treasure, with Becky he gets lost in a cave.and finally,they find a box of gold. My favourite scene in the book is when everyone thinks Tom is dead.He decides to go to his own funeral.He hides and watches for a time and then suddenly he appears. Everyone is astonished to see him but they're also pleased to see him alive. Tom is the hero of the story,but there are other important characters.Huck is an outsider and everyone ...\n\nQ: .The whole book is mainly about   _   .", "options": ["freedom and social rules", "children's bad behaviour", "the growth of young children", "strangers in American small towns"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 473, "question": "It is not a secret that these are _ times that put everyone on edge all the time and it makes people angry with their families, co-workers, friends and relatives, frustrated and highly annoyed just for the noise of the neighbors or the music coming from the opposite house. Anger and negative energy have a strong influence on everyone's life, even when they don't realize it. Being in a calm state of mind is simply wonderful. Results of this can be seen when parents no longer shout at their children over any small thing and when one can keep him cool when bad things happen and doesn't let the situation become worse by his negative influence. Also results can be seen on a larger scale. In 1993 a very interesting scientific experiment called The US Transcendental Meditation experiment was cond...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is NOT true according to the passage?", "options": ["Violent crimes are closely related to aggressive characters.", "People are sometimes easily annoyed by small things.", "Many people fail to carry out a meditation method.", "Meditation can cure people of many illnesses."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3281, "question": "Boxing was long viewed sickly. Generally forbidden by law in earlier days, the fighting was usually done with bare fists, and matches often lasted forty or fifty rounds. In 1882 John L. Sullivan, a fighter of great power, won the world heavyweight championship from Paddy Ryan in a bare fisted battle marked by hitting, scratching, and biting without any rule. Five years later, while fighting Patsy Cardiff at Minneapolis, Sullivan broke his right arm in the third round, but he continued fighting to the sixth round and won. In 1889, Sullivan defeated Jade Kilrain with his bare fists in another championship fight, winning twenty thousand dollars and a diamond prize medal. His admirers talked then of running him for the next governor, but he traveled to Australia for a boxing tour instead, comi...\n\nQ: Sullivan's fight with Kilrain was   _  .", "options": ["the first boxing championship match", "a bare-fisted championship fight", "the last boxing match to be fought bare-fisted", "a six-round match"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2712, "question": "Without any previous notice, a documentary dominated headlines and social websites over the weekend. Under the Dome, a 103-minute documentary self-funded by former CCTV news anchor Chai Jing was released on video-sharing websites in China on Feb 28. It has rapidly pushed the public awareness about air pollution and encouraged people to join in efforts to make a difference. Chai, 39, said she started the work out of her \"personal clashes\" with smog after she gave birth to a daughter. \"I sealed tight all the windows. I started every day by checking the air pollution index,\" Chai said. Millions of other people are also doing the same. While they stop there, Chai goes deeper. \"I don't want to live in this way. 1 need to find out where the smog comes from and what on earth is going on.\" Over a ...\n\nQ: Why Chai jing decided to make the film at first ?", "options": ["She wanted to do something for her daughter", "She wanted to disclose loopholes in car emissions regulations.", "She wanted to make money", "She wanted to raise public attention toward the structure of the energy industry"], "answer": 0}]